d'escoto
d'escoto
and everything is fine everything is correct
y todo bien todo correcto
[Music] I
[Música]
have kids,
tengo niños
kids, almost the same when I look at what
chavales casi igual al mirar lo que
I have here, some little bell what do you
tengo aquí una alguna campanilla que me
say live like 30,000 like like 35 thousand
dices live like 30.000 like como 35 mil
light kids kids today I have
light chavales chavales hoy tengo
a joke prepared for Lorena that you don't
preparado una broma para lorena que no
see, you don't see, she neither expects it
veas que no veas es que ni se lo esperas
nor does she expect it how many subscribers
ni se lo espera cuántos suscriptores
how much her Christ in the studio just came to me with
cuánto su cristo del estudio se me acaba
a brilliant idea okay I'm going to
de ocurrir una idea brillante vale voy a
be here playing the console and I'm going to
estar aquí jugando a la consola y la voy
ignore her for 24 hours I'm going to ignore her for 24
a ignorar 24 horas la voy a ignorar 24
hours okay and she's going to freak out she's going to freak
horas vale y se va a rallar se va a
you out like crazy and she's going to go crazy she's going to
rallar que te cagas y se va a volver
go very very very crazy okay it was wow wow wow wow I don't even want to imagine her reaction, it was worth it, the mess she's going to make so nothing are kids let's put the camera let's take this one which is the small camera okay and I'm going to hide it in a place where I can't see it here
en un sitio donde no la vea aquí
perfectly okay well and what the [ __ ]
perfectamente vale bueno y qué [__]
what the [ __ ] I'm going to put a small
qué [__] voy a poner aquí un pequeño
spotlight here because I little  because if the video doesn't stay
foco porque yo poco porque si no queda
then we're going to put a little bit here yes yes I
entonces vamos a poner aquí un poco sí
think she won't notice anything easy I
sí yo creo que no notará nada fácil yo
think she won't suspect anything she
creo que no sospechara nada ella no
has no idea they have no idea I
tiene ni idea ellos no tiene ni idea
imagine she won't remember that I'm a
imagino que no se acordará de que soy
youtuber extraction of some [ __ ]
youtuber extracción de algunas
kids she just sent me a
de chavales me acaba de mandar un
message and told me that she's uploading
mensaje y me ha dicho que está subiendo
okay through this door through this door
vale por esta puerta por esta puerta de
here she's going to upload at any moment so let's
aquí va a subir en cualquier momento así
go inside video
que vamos dentro vídeo
because it wasn't a kid here it wasn't
porque no era chaval aquí no era
[Music]
[Música]
xavi
xavi
that
eso
go calm down calm down I haven't
vaya tranquilo tranquilo que todavía no
come back yet well up yes I hadn't
he vuelto bueno arriba de sí que no me
become [ __ ] no but at
había vuelto subnormal no pero por lo
least at least not that kind of
menos por lo menos no de ese tipo
[ __ ] today I bring you the new fashion on
subnormal hoy os traigo la nueva moda en
youtube
youtube
here the fashion you know that it was changing
aquí la moda ya sabéis que iba cambiando
very quickly like almost a week I
muy rápidamente como casi a la semana no
did nothing we were with the box of the
hacía nada estábamos con la caja de la
web nothing ago we were also with the
web hace nada estuvimos también con los
pitchers first with the jokes he
pitcheres primer con las bromas a mi
stuck my girlfriend with duct tape anyway
novia la pegó con cinta americana en fin
all these things that
todas estas cosas que siempre la hacen
the same youtubers always do we have a group of if I
los mismos youtubers tenemos un grupo de
were here in the community of
yo estuviera aquí en la comunidad de
others Spain that what they do is all
otros españa que lo que hacen es todas
the  fashions okay the same ones are
las modas vale los mismos te están
summoning the devil they are summoning
invocando al demonio que están invocando
pikachu they bring you a box of
a pikachu que te traen una caja de lalín
web lalin that they put in the closet all
web que se meten en el armario toda la
night and their name does not realize that they
noche y su nombre no se da cuenta que se
get into a bathtub of jelly anyway
meten en una bañera de gelatina en fin
where do they get these ideas do they copy them from
de donde sacan estas ideas las copian de
the American community specifically I
la comunidad americana en concreto yo
think from youtuber trusts to put
creo que desde youtuber confía poner
here on the screen which by the way I think
aquí en la pantalla que por cierto creo
has some kind of
que tiene algún tipo de
in the mouth because I do not know why all
en la boca porque no sé por qué todas
the thumbnails are like
las miniaturas
this it looks like a [ __ ]
las pone así parece una [__] muñeca
inflatable doll what I do not understand is what
hinchable yo lo que no entiendo es qué
kind of couples do these people have that they
tipo de parejas tienen esta gente que
are always falling for their joke and
siempre están cayendo en su broma y en
their things because it is normal if you
sus cosas porque está de normal si tú
have a boyfriend who is youtube if you
tienes un novio que es youtube si tú
are seeing that he is ignoring you the
estás viendo que te está ignorando lo
first thing that has to cross your
primero que se te tiene que pasar por la
mind without another person or the fight or
cabeza sin otra persona ni la pelea ni
anything and the guy goes around the house with a camera that
nada y el chava van con una cámara por
is recording some video what
la casa que está grabando algún vídeo lo
some [ __ ] is doing for
que está haciendo alguna [__] para
some of his videos in this occasion the
algunos de sus vídeos en esta ocasión la
joke to call it somehow
broma por llamarlo de alguna forma
because he does not have a type of jokes this is about
porque no tiene un tipo de bromas esta
ignoring his girlfriend during  24
trata de ignorar a su novia durante 24
hours you always have to keep in mind
horas tenéis que tener en cuenta siempre
that when you do an internet challenge
que cuando se hace un reto de internet
that is 24 hours they actually
que sea 24 horas en realidad quieren
mean three hours or two hours that
decir tres horas o dos horas los que
take to record it just so happens that
tarden en graba da la casualidad de que
usually the girlfriends of these
por lo general las novias de estos
youtubers tend to be very heavy very
youtubers suelen ser muy pesadas muy
heavy no I probably make my
pesadas no yo seguramente le haga mi
girlfriend this this this is this chalet
novia este este este está este chalé
this joke whatever they want to call it and she doesn't even
esta broma como lo quieran llamar y ni
realize because if my girlfriend goes from
se da cuenta porque si mi novia pasa de
me
mí
only to that
sólo a ello
or I mean I'm back from ignoring my
o sea yo la vuelta de ignorando a mi
girlfriend 24 hours and surely it's not that I
novia 24 horas y seguramente no es que
realize that I would be super
me se dé cuenta que estaría súper a
comfortable no no although I am all day
gusto no no si bien estoy todo el día a
nobody
nadie me están jodiendo pues no las
is screwing me well no the girlfriends of these youtubers just have to be doing this chalet for it to get heavier even around the neck talk to me please what's wrong with you I hook my neck I pull my ear everything let's see everything and we're going to analyze specifically 4 that I have taken from
analizar en concreto 4 que he cogido de
the best there is
lo mejor que hay
okay from the best there is right now in
vale de lo mejor que hay ahora mismo en
the community of Spain that specifically
la comunidad de españa que concretamente
this group always do these things
este grupo siempre hacen estas cosas
always so if you have to call
siempre o sea que si hay que llamar
devil they call it yes there is whatever whatever it is they are
demonio lo llaman que sí hay que lo que
always sellouts
sea lo que sea siempre están vendidos
of course I want to make it clear that I have
por supuesto quiero aclarar que no tengo
nothing against these youtubers nor am I
nada en contra de estos youtube ni que
going to insult them or anything in
vaya a insultarlos ni mucho menos de
fact hey if it works and makes them money
hecho oye si le funciona y les da dinero
up front maybe I would too well I wouldn't
por delante quizás yo también bueno yo
do that but anyway the thing is that it
no haría eso pero bueno el tema es que
works the thing is that this
funciona que el tema es que esto
works we don't know why but for
funciona no sabemos por qué pero por
some reason in life these videos
algún motivo de la vida estos vídeos
work in fact I more from the
funcionan de hecho yo más del canal del
jon mansion show channel
show de jon mansión
did a test on his channel and had a
hizo una prueba en su canal y tuvo un
result of double the views an hour
resultado de el doble de visitas la hora
than normal making this type of
de lo normal haciendo este tipo de
videos what is true is that I don't
vídeos lo que sí que es verdad que no me
like that you use his girlfriends in the
gusta que utilices a sus novias en la
thumbnail for this and not because you put my
miniatura para esto y no por poner mi
girlfriend no no because you put my girlfriend no no not to
novia no no por poner mi novia no no
use her but since you show her as a
usarla sino ya que la muestran como
sexual claim okay because at least you are not
reclamo sexual vale porque al menos no
going to agree with me and let me
va a estar de acuerdo conmigo y me
explain I totally agree
explico yo estoy totalmente de acuerdo
that every woman and every man dresses
en que cada mujer y cada hombre vistan
however they want we are not in
como quieran no estamos en la época de
Franco's time or anything and all
franco ni mucho menos y todas las
women have the right like the rest of the
mujeres tienen derecho como el resto de
people to dress however they want not that they
personas a vestirse como quieran no que
want to wear a low neckline that they
se quieren poner un escote que se
want to wear culottes  but what
quieren poner un culotte pero lo que a
I don't think is right is that a boyfriend
mí no me parece bien es que un novio
uses his girlfriend as a sexual lure
utilice a su novia como reclamo sexual
to get more views, I don't know if we
para ganar más visitas no sé si esto lo
can even call this a form of
podemos llamar incluso una forma de
prostitution, it seems really extreme to me, I didn't
prostitución me parece muy bestia no
want to go too far, but rather like exposing her
quería pasarme pero sí como exponerla
as if she were a steak in a
como si se tratara de un filete en un
butcher shop window and now
escaparate de una carnicería y ahora
when we see the videos maybe I'll be
cuando veamos los vídeos quizás me dé la
right, I mean, to give you an idea,
razón o sea para que os hagáis una idea
I have more views
yo tengo más vistas las bragas y los
of these girlfriends' panties and bras on
sujetadores de las novias de estos
YouTube than on my own, that's
youtube que de la mía propia
it, I'm right. First, let's go for
es eso estoy derecho primero vamos a
anything, okay, not this one, everyone already knows it, it does
todo vale no a éste ya lo conoce todo el
n't have almost two million
mundo no tiene casi dos millones de
subscribers and almost all the thumbnails
suscriptores y casi todas las miniaturas
show his girlfriend in bed breastfeeding, I mean,
sale su novia en la cama en braza o sea
almost everyone. I don't understand the reason, I
casi todos no entiendo el por tivo lo
understand it because I repeat it again, I
entiendo es porque lo vuelvo a repetir
have nothing personal against
no tengo nada en contra personal con
any of Toyota, look, I'm only
ningunos de toyota ver solamente estoy
talking about their content, let's
hablando de sus contenidos vamos a
start with the way it is, everything is going well,
empezar por la forma que tiene todo va
prepare the joke, I mean,
lindes preparar la broma es decir
place the camera strategically so
colocar la cámara estratégicamente para
that the girlfriend doesn't notice
que la novia no se dé cuenta
[Music]
[Música]
well, this small camera
bueno es que esta cámara la pequeña
that's the little tocalli but I want to
esa es la pequeña tocalli pero me quiero
imagine and how will it be done the big ones the
imaginar y cómo se hará las grandes a la
big one that is what carries a stool
grande que es lo que lleva un taburete
of these of those that they are going to sit on
de esto de los que van a sentar en
telecinco and they go stealing like that by the
telecinco y van robando así por el
palmas but he suggested how are you going to leave that
palmas pero sugirió cómo vas a dejar ese
piece of camera on that it is that it is
pedazo de cámara encendía que es que
also the camera on with the
está además la cámara encendía con la
screen looking at you or rather you can see
pantalla mirando para ti o sea que se ve
perfectly that it is recording how is
perfectamente que está grabando como no
your girlfriend going to notice that to
se va a dar cuenta tu novia de que a
leave the dresser that piece of camera if
dejar la cómoda ese pedazo de cámara si
I take off my jeans and
yo me quito los pantalones vaqueros y
let them hang by the door and my partner
los dejo colgar la puerta y mi parienta
is already scolding me for not having
ya me está echando la bronca por no
put it in the closet answer
haberlo metió en el armario contesta
[Music]
[Música]
constable answer me you
condestable contéstame
are an idiot seriously
es [__] en serio
and about the [ __ ] day no more
y sobre el [__] día ya no
and here I have to tell you some things worth
y aquí tengo que deciros cositas vale a
615 million visits a month I think it will
615 millones de visitas al mes yo creo
give you to buy a headboard
que te da para comprarte un cabecero
for the bed and two the most important thing is what
para la cama y dos lo más importante es
I was saying in this case my wife would not
lo que yo decía en este caso mi mujer no
be scolding me because I did not
estaría echando la bronca porque no le
speak to her that soir ytor damn it would be
hablase eso le soir yátor [__] estaría
hitting me with ops already for getting into
pegándome de ops ya por meterme en la
bed with that [ __ ] in my socks
cama con esa [__] en los calcetines
kids who are the ones that are white
hijos que son los que se tienen blanco
with black soles
con la suela negra
take off their stinky socks
quítate en sus calcetines apestosos
and I'm having a terrible time
y lo estoy pasando fatal
we have two things left
nos quedan dos cosas
because they have made things as
porque me han hecho de las cosas como
they are
son
hey aggressive easy and aggressive that the
oye agresiva fácil y agresiva que yo lo
most I expected from you and that you
máximo que me esperaba de ti y que le
gave him a strike they call me freddy this
pusieras un strike me llaman freddy este
youtube more of the same well
youtube más de los mismos bien pues
freddy not content with making a video
freddy no contento con hacer un vídeo
ignoring his girlfriend as he saw that it
ignorando a su novia como vio que le
worked very well for him he has 22 videos
funcionaba muy bien tiene 22 vídeos
ignoring his girlfriend but what
ignorando a su novia pero es que lo que
catches my attention is that the
me llama la atención es que sale la
girlfriend appears in a towel in the two thumbnails
novia en toalla en las dos miniaturas
that I have seen the entire videos and at
que he visto los vídeos entero y en
no time does that scene appear or rather at
ningún momento sale esa escena o sea en
no time does the girlfriend appear in the shower
ningún momento sale la novia en la ducha
and the thing is that this youtube
y es que este youtube
shows the girlfriend with some sexual claim
saca a la novia con algún reclamo sexual
either in an air or with a towel
ya sea en pompa ya sea con una toalla
whatever the video is
sea el vídeo de lo que sea
or rather surely this kid if he
o sea seguramente este chaval si se
had formed and the
hubiera forma y saldría en la miniatura
girlfriend with a towel would appear in the thumbnail surely later
la novia con una toalla seguro después
we have the ex actor who you already know everything
tenemos al ex actor que ya sabéis todo
is a gem not a legend  who I
que es una joya no una leyenda a quien
had Spain and he wants to belong to
yo tuve españa y él quiere pertenecer a
this group he wants to belong to this
este grupo él quiere pertenecer a este
group that makes these types of videos
grupo que hace estos tipos de vídeos
but what's the problem he doesn't have a
pero cuál es el problema que no tiene
girlfriend this is the foster sector and he
novia esto es el sector acogida y ha
said I don't have a girlfriend [ __ ]
dicho que no tengo novia a tomar por
my father himself and it wasn't my father
culo a mi padre mismo y no era mi padre
24 hours it couldn't have been
24 horas no podría haber quedado
funny no I even have to admit
gracioso no incluso tengo que reconocer
that I laughed a few times with the
que he echado alguna carcajada con el
father watching the video but the success is
padre viendo el vídeo pero el éxito es
mine is that the [ __ ] is going to start the
lo mío es que la [__] va a comenzar el
video
vídeo
and since I always speak Catalan with my parents I
y como con mis padres siempre hablo
told him that I was going to record a blog
catalán le dije que iba a grabar un blog
and that please when the
y que por favor cuando estuviera la
camera was in front he should speak Spanish to see
cámara delante hablara castellano a ver
if it works or rather your father speaks Catalan
si cuela o sea tu padre habla catalán
but you warned him that you were going to record
pero tú le has avisado que vas a grabar
and that's why in the video he speaks in Spanish
y por eso en el vídeo habla en español
but it turns out you're ignoring him
pero resulta que le estás ignorando
so your father is not supposed to
entonces se supone que tu padre no tiene
suspect that you're doing some
que sospechar que estás haciendo alguna
[ __ ] for a youtuber no but oh well
[__] para youtuber no pero bueno los
this kid's subscribers eat anything
suscriptores de este chaval se comen lo
in fact he has his own channel videos
que sea de hecho tiene su canal vídeos
what do I call momo I think I found
como llamo a momo creo que he encontrado
a real fairy in my house q nothing I
un hada real en mi casa q nada me
found a real elf  in my house fly
encontré un duende real en mi casa vuela
for five minutes with this trick a [ __ ]
por cinco minutos con este truco un [__]
tutorial to fly a [ __ ] tutorial
tutorial para volar un [__] tutorial
to fly I want to see it
para volar quiero verlo
but a little bit of germs together like this
pero un poco de gérmenes juntas así
interlace the fingers so that they remain like the
entrelaza los dedos que queden como los
fingers like this together
dedos así juntos
and more or less without looking [ __ ]
y más o menos sin parecer subnormales
Diego state to the ex-editor that of putting
estado diego al exeditor eso de poner
more of that in my house and not looking
más eso en mi casa y no parecer
[ __ ] and last but not least
subnormal y por último y no menos
that anima kim ann mack and mar
importante que anima kim ann mack y mar
more of the same not miniature by
más de lo mismo no miniatura en
miniature a little sexy not good
miniatura un poco sexy no bueno
miniatures putting his girlfriend totally or
miniaturas poniendo a su novia total o
rather is it in what context of a video do you
sea es que en qué contexto de un vídeo
use your girlfriend like that for the
utilizas así a tu novia para la
miniature I don't know what the music video
miniatura a no sé qué sea el videoclip
of the cal osha is
de la cal osha
that yes imagine has been the smartest and most
eso sí imaginar ha sido el más listo y
attentive let's see how the video ends
atento vamos a ver cómo acaba el vídeo
not only right now people
no solamente ahora mismo gente
[Music]
[Música]
today
hoy
ah
ah
and I'm going to leave it here guys
y lo voy a dejar hasta aquí chicos lo
I'm going to do it until there Valencia we're
voy a hacer hasta allí valencia
going to rest I am if you
lo vamos a descansar estoy les haya
liked it a lot we continue or it is made to
gustado muchísimo seguimos o se hace
think that there will be a few from now
pensar que habrá unas cuantas de ahora
ignoring the girlfriend and the girlfriend comes to him
ignorando a la novia y le viene la novia
and says to him from there the one of the
y le dice la de ahí la de la del
exhibitionist there is no low ignore
exhibicionista no hay de baja ignorar
now I imagine the  From now on and until
ahora me imagino la de ahora y hasta sin
what animal goes for the fourth says well
qué animal se va por cuarto dice bueno
I endorsed here we were the challenge
yo avalé aquí estábamos el reto se acabó
the challenge is over a great machines and nothing
el reto un gran de máquinas y nada
guys this has been all the video for
chavales esto ha sido todo el vídeo de
today I hope you had a laugh and
hoy espero que hayáis echar unas risas y
show me with a good like
así demostrármelo con un buen like
subscribe if you don't know me and
suscribiros si no me conocéis y nos
see you in the next one
vemos en el siguiente